visitkochijapan.com 2016-10-30

# Privacy Policy - VISIT KOCHI JAPAN

### Privacy Policy

  * Kochi Visitors & Convention Association

As a general rule, you do not need to provide personal information such as your name and address in order to browse this website. 

The association sometimes outsources the maintenance and operation of this website to a third party. Even in that event, however, the association fully ensures proper management of the website at its contractor to prevent users’ browsing history, personal information and other data from leaking out and to protect against unauthorized access. 

The association will never disclose users’ browsing history and personal information to a third party other than its contractor without securing user permission. But the association could disclose such information without obtaining user consent if required by law to do so, or if requested to do so by public organizations such as courts and police. 

  * Disclaimers

The association exercises due care in posting information on its website, but regardless of circumstances it does not guarantee the integrity, accuracy, newness, usefulness and other aspects of the content of such information. Furthermore, the association asks for your understanding in advance that it will not assume responsibility for any consequences of a user’s decision or action based on the information posted on the website. 

All of the information posted the website is the information available at the time of posting. Names, content and other information are subject to change without advance notice, and information posted on the website could become outdated over time. 

The website’s addresses, including that of its home page, are subject to change without notice. Please note that the association will not assume responsibility for any consequences users may face such as a broken link or webpage display disorder caused by an address change.
